(this["webpackJsonpreact-app"]=this["webpackJsonpreact-app"]||[]).push([[0],{13:function(e){e.exports=JSON.parse('[{"id":1,"score":"$500"},{"id":2,"score":"$1,000"},{"id":3,"score":"$2,000"},{"id":4,"score":"$4,000"},{"id":5,"score":"$16,000"},{"id":6,"score":"$32,000"},{"id":7,"score":"$64,000"},{"id":8,"score":"$125,000"},{"id":9,"score":"$250,000"},{"id":10,"score":"$500,000"},{"id":11,"score":"$1,000,000"}]')},24:function(e){e.exports=JSON.parse('[{"id":1,"question":"In what children\'s game are participants chased by someone designated \\"It\\"?","content":["Tag","Simon Says","Charades","Hopscotch"],"correct":"Tag"},{"id":2,"question":"On a radio, stations are changed by using what control?","content":["Tuning","Volume","Bass","Treble"],"correct":"Tuning"},{"id":3,"question":"Which material is most dense?","content":["Silver","Styrofoam","Butter","Gold"],"correct":"Gold"},{"id":4,"question":"Which state in the United States is largest by area?","content":["Alaska","California","Texas","Hawaii"],"correct":"Alaska"},{"id":5,"question":"What is Aurora Borealis commonly known as?","content":["Fairy Dust","Northern Lights","Book of ages","Game of Thrones"],"correct":"Northern Lights"},{"id":6,"question":"Will I get an offer from Genesis?","content":["Yes","Of course","Sure, bro","All above"],"correct":"Sure, bro"},{"id":7,"question":"What is commonly known as the \\"Emerald City\\" in the United States?","content":["Palos Verdes, CA","Seattle, WA","New York, NY","Dallas, TX"],"correct":"Seattle, WA"},{"id":8,"question":"What is the national emblem of Canada?","content":["Maple Leaf","Brown Bear","Maple Syrup","Waffle"],"correct":"Maple Leaf"},{"id":9,"question":"Oscar Awards were instituted in","content":["1968","1929","1901","1965"],"correct":"1929"},{"id":10,"question":"When did Margaret Thatcher became the first female Prime Minister of Britain?","content":["1998","1989","1979","1800"],"correct":"1979"},{"id":11,"question":"An albino gorilla usually has what color for?","content":["Brown","Black","White","Golden"],"correct":"White"},{"id":12,"question":"When did China test their first atomic device?","content":["1962","1963","1964","1965"],"correct":"1964"}]')},30:function(e,t,n){},31:function(e,t,n){},32:function(e,t,n){},38:function(e,t,n){},39:function(e,t,n){},55:function(e,t,n){},56:function(e,t,n){"use strict";n.r(t);var c=n(1),s=n(0),i=n(16),a=n.n(i),r=n(9),o=(n(30),n(2)),d=(n(31),n(32),function(){return Object(c.jsx)("div",{className:"wrapper",children:Object(c.jsxs)("div",{className:"App",children:[Object(c.jsx)("div",{className:"App__main-image"}),Object(c.jsxs)("div",{className:"App__main main",children:[Object(c.jsxs)("h1",{className:"main__title",children:["Who wants to be",Object(c.jsx)("br",{}),"a millionaire?"]}),Object(c.jsx)(r.b,{to:"/game",children:Object(c.jsx)("button",{type:"button",className:"main__btn",children:"Start"})})]})]})})}),l=n(11),b=(n(38),n(39),n(12)),j=n.n(b),u=n(23),m=n(13),h=function(e){var t=e.counter;return Object(c.jsxs)(c.Fragment,{children:[Object(c.jsx)("div",{className:"scores",children:m.map((function(e){return Object(c.jsx)("div",{className:j()(t===e.id?"scores__item--active":"scores__item"),children:e.score},e.id)}))}),Object(c.jsx)(u.stack,{right:!0,width:"100%",disableAutoFocus:!0,itemListElement:"div",children:m.map((function(e){return Object(c.jsx)("div",{className:j()(t===e.id?"scores__item--active":"scores__item"),children:Object(c.jsx)("div",{children:e.score})})}))})]})},O=["A","B","C","D"],p=function(e){var t=e.answer,n=e.checkAnswer,s=e.selectedAnswer,i=e.index;return Object(c.jsx)("div",{className:j()(s===t?"list__option--selected":"list__option"),role:"button",onClick:function(){return n(t)},children:Object(c.jsxs)("p",{className:"list__option-text",children:[Object(c.jsx)("span",{className:"list__option-letter",children:O[i]}),t]})},t)},x=n(24),f=function(){var e=Object(s.useState)(1),t=Object(l.a)(e,2),n=t[0],i=t[1],a=Object(s.useState)(0),r=Object(l.a)(a,2),d=r[0],b=r[1],j=Object(s.useState)(""),u=Object(l.a)(j,2),O=u[0],f=u[1],_=Object(s.useState)(!0),v=Object(l.a)(_,2),g=v[0],N=v[1],y=Object(s.useState)(!1),w=Object(l.a)(y,2),S=w[0],A=w[1],q=Object(s.useState)("$0"),k=Object(l.a)(q,2),W=k[0],$=k[1],B=function(e){f(e),A(!0)},T=function(){b(d+1),m.some((function(e){return n===e.id?$(e.score):null}))};return Object(c.jsxs)("div",{className:"Game",children:[Object(c.jsx)("div",{className:"Game__body body",children:x.map((function(e){return e.id===n&&Object(c.jsxs)(c.Fragment,{children:[Object(c.jsx)("h3",{className:"body__question",children:"".concat(e.question," (").concat(e.correct,")")},e.id),Object(c.jsx)("button",{type:"button",className:S?"body__question-btn--visible":"body__question-btn",onClick:function(){return t=e.id,n=e.correct,void(O===n?(i(t+1),A(!1),T()):N(!1));var t,n},children:"Submit"}),Object(c.jsx)("div",{className:"body__list list",children:e.content.map((function(t){return Object(c.jsx)(p,{index:e.content.indexOf(t),answer:t,checkAnswer:B,selectedAnswer:O})}))})]})}))}),Object(c.jsx)(h,{counter:d}),(d>=12||!g)&&Object(c.jsx)(o.a,{to:"gameover/:".concat(W)})]})},_=(n(55),function(e){var t=e.history.location.pathname.slice(11);return Object(c.jsxs)("div",{className:"game-over",children:[Object(c.jsx)("div",{className:"game-over__image"}),Object(c.jsxs)("div",{className:"game-over__main main",children:[Object(c.jsxs)("p",{className:"main__text",children:[Object(c.jsx)("span",{children:"Total score:"}),Object(c.jsx)("br",{}),"".concat(t," earned")]}),Object(c.jsx)(r.b,{to:"/",children:Object(c.jsx)("button",{type:"button",className:"main__btn",children:"Try again"})})]})]})}),v=function(){return Object(c.jsxs)(o.d,{children:[Object(c.jsx)(o.b,{path:"/gameover",component:_}),Object(c.jsx)(o.b,{path:"/game",component:f}),Object(c.jsx)(o.b,{path:"/",exact:!0,component:d}),Object(c.jsx)(o.b,{render:function(){return Object(c.jsx)("h1",{children:"404: page not found"})}})]})};a.a.render(Object(c.jsx)(r.a,{basename:"/millionaire-game",children:Object(c.jsx)(v,{})}),document.getElementById("root"))}},[[56,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.fe251f8c.chunk.js.map